{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1786","name":"Burger King","address":"20240 Plymouth Rd","zipcode":"48228","owner":"EYM King of Michigan LLC","licenseNumber":"078378","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.23905,42.37193","geojson":{"id":"1786","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.239050167,42.371926869]},"properties":{"name":"Burger King","owner":"EYM King of Michigan LLC","address":"20240 Plymouth Rd","zipcode":"48228","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"078378","establishmentid":"1786","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5299","name":"Plymouth Ocean Delight- Manhattan Fish","address":"20100 Plymouth Rd Suite B","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"977","name":"Olympia Coney Island","address":"20040 Plymouth Rd","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"5025","name":"New Bentley Lounge","address":"19631 Plymouth Rd","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"2471","name":"Ply Produce and Deli","address":"19615 Plymouth Rd","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"1241","name":"Mann Elementary School","address":"19625 Elmira St","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"5176","name":"Mary's Grill #2","address":"20804 Plymouth","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"991","name":"Rouge Park Golf Course","address":"11701 Burt Rd","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"3447","name":"Detroit Community Schools","address":"12675 Burt Rd","zipcode":"48223"},{"establishmentid":"4816","name":"WAY Academy West Campus","address":"19321 Chicago W","zipcode":"48228"},{"establishmentid":"4823","name":"City Covenant Church","address":"13624 Stout","zipcode":"48223"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44744","inspectionDate":"2019-01-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Utensil(s) and equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"42709","inspectionDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."}]},{"inspectionid":"42376","inspectionDate":"2018-05-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41227","inspectionDate":"2018-01-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"39486","inspectionDate":"2017-08-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.116","violationDescription":"Concentration of the SANITIZING solution shall be accurately determined by using a test kit or other device. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use test kit to verify sanitizer concentration."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"38828","inspectionDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"37350","inspectionDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Not provided (with) DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"mop","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"The Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-04-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1786"}}